或许这就是问题所在... 你一直在做对的事情
Maybe that's the problem... you always do the right thing.
或许是时候错一错了
Maybe it's time to do the wrong thing.
就像你现在这样?
Like you're doing right now?
是的
Exactly.
我一遍又一遍地问你愿不愿意
I asked you over and over if you were okay.
你既然不愿意 又何必要参加婚礼?
Why would you go through with the wedding if you weren't?
我本来觉得自己愿意 但结果并非如此
I thought I was okay, but it turns out I'm not.
好吧 听着 我可能没做到百分百的真诚
Okay, listen, I may not have been entirely faithful,
但是你 抬你真的不容易啊!
but you, you are not easy to lift!
哇哦!
Wow!
结了婚就是不一样
Well, marriage must agree with you.
你简直红光焕发啊
Well, you are just glowing.
我才没红光焕发
I'm not glowing.
我生着气呢
I'm upset.
不管是什么 你看起来很不错
Well, whatever it is, it agrees with you.
咚咚咚 Penny?
Knock, knock, knock, Penny?
咚咚咚 Penny? 咚咚咚 Penny?
Knock, knock, knock, Penny? Knock, knock, knock, Penny?
这是干什么?
What's this?
Leonard把事情告诉我了
Leonard told me what happened,
所以我就自发给你做了点热饮
so I took it upon myself to make you a hot beverage.
你真贴心啊
Oh. That's so sweet of you.
是啊 我知道
Yeah. I know.
不过 在这世道
Turns out, being sweet
单单贴心可留不住女孩
isn't enough to keep a girl these days.
暗指麦当娜的歌曲拜金女孩material girl
我觉得要怪麦当娜
I blame Madonna.
你和Amy分手的事真是可惜
I'm sorry to hear about you and Amy.
关于Leonard 也是可惜
Well, I'm sorry about Leonard.
我以为自己已经把他调教好了
Thought I raised him better than that.
本来这事就够糟糕了
You know, it's bad enough what happened,
他还试图隐瞒他每天
but then he tried to hide the fact that he sees her
都在学校里看见她的事实
all the time at the university.
每天都见? 是谁啊?
He does? Who is it?
一个叫Mandy的女孩
Some girl named Mandy.
- Mandy Chao?  - 就这货
- Mandy Chao?  - Yeah.
你没必要担心人家啦
Oh, you don't need to worry about her.
她智慧和美丽兼具
She's brilliant and attractive.
她才看不上Leonard呢
She can do way better than Leonard.
真好啊
That's great.
等一等
Wait a minute.
我知道这听起来有点不靠谱
I know this may sound farfetched,
但我现在单身待售呢
but I'm on the market now.
我要是跟Mandy约会
You know, if I dated Mandy,
算是同时给Leonard和Amy一个教训
that would teach both Leonard and Amy a lesson.
太荒谬了
That's ridiculous.
嗯 你说得对 我不能跟一个自尊心低到
Oh, you're right. I could never be with a woman
跟Leonard约会的人在一起
whose self-esteem was so low she'd be with Leonard.
我跟Leonard在一起呢
I'm with Leonard.
嗯 我知道 回不了头了
Yeah, I know. Forever.
真想不到会走到今天这一步？
Who would have believed these things would happen to us?
对吧？
Right?
不敢相信Amy真的说到做到了
I can't believe Amy actually went through with it.
等下
Hang on.
你早就知道她要跟我分手？
You knew that she was going to end it with me?
你有试着阻止她吗？
Did you try and stop her?
我告诉她听从自己的想法做让她开心的事
I told her to be true to herself and do what makes her happy.
做让她开心的事？
Do what makes her happy?
她会弹竖琴 而且车付了全款
She plays the harp and her car is paid for.
她还想要多快乐？
How much happier can she be?
好吧 听着 她觉得你是个糟糕的男友
Okay, look, it's not my fault
不是我的错
that she thought you were a bad boyfriend.